<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Nonsense | Kernow Soul]]></title>
  <link href="http://kernowsoul.com/blog/tags/nonsense/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://kernowsoul.com/"/>
  <updated>2014-03-21T14:54:07+00:00</updated>
  <id>http://kernowsoul.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Jamie Dyer]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[My new business cards have arrived]]></title>
    <link href="http://kernowsoul.com/blog/2008/09/26/my-new-business-cards-have-arrived/"/>
    <updated>2008-09-26T17:55:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://kernowsoul.com/blog/2008/09/26/my-new-business-cards-have-arrived</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I&rsquo;ve been making do with some terrible old business cards for the last few years and thought it was about time for some nice new ones. I wanted to go for something clean and simple so designed them with just a little type, a bit of custom kerning then shot them off to the <a href="http://moo.com">nice little moo bot</a> for printing. I have to say I do quite like the playful tone and little touches moo uses in their communications, it makes you feel happy.</p>

<p><img src="http://kernowsoul.com/images/uploaded/business-card.jpg" alt="Jamie Dyer business card" /></p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[UK does it better... I agree]]></title>
    <link href="http://kernowsoul.com/blog/2008/09/21/uk-does-it-better-i-agree/"/>
    <updated>2008-09-21T14:43:00+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://kernowsoul.com/blog/2008/09/21/uk-does-it-better-i-agree</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>So the rain has backed off for the first sustained period since I moved back to the UK, I&rsquo;ve taken the opportunity to lay on the grass in the sun and read a book I picked up the other day, <a href="http://punkmarketing.com">Punk Marketing</a>. Not that far in and I&rsquo;m all ready enjoying it, who would have thought a book on marketing could be entertaining!</p>

<p>I came across a quote I thought I would share&hellip;</p>

<blockquote><p>&ldquo;Go to a multiplex, sit through the ads, and see how abused you feel by the start of the movie. Then to to a cinema in the UK and motive that most people turn up to view those commercials. Because they are actually fun-sensible and intriguing and full of messages that make people applaud.Yes, shout out with glee! These are entertaining, funny, well-produced, and cool. Four terms you&rsquo;d never use to describe an ad at movies in the US of A today.&rdquo;</p></blockquote>

<p>I couldn&rsquo;t agree more, those poor Canadians are force fed the majority the USA&rsquo;s crappy ads. What&rsquo;s probably worse is that often the product or service isn&rsquo;t even available to them! I digress, having suffered with the Canadians for the last three years I can say I would gladly watch several hours of English commercials than a single US ad break.</p>

<p>In closing&hellip; Well done Britain, we produce some of the best ads in the world.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
